Welcome to the Example Subtitle File!
This is a demonstration of SRT subtitles.
You can use SRT files to add subtitles to your videos.
Each subtitle entry consists of a number, a timecode, and the subtitle text.
The timecode format is hours:minutes:seconds,milliseconds.
You can adjust the timing to match your video.
Make sure the subtitle text is clear and readable.
Keep your subtitles short and easy to understand.
Avoid placing too much text on the screen at once.
Sync the subtitles carefully with the spoken audio.
Review your subtitles before publishing your video.
Good subtitles improve viewer engagement.
They also make your content accessible to a wider audience.
Now you know the basics of creating an SRT file.
Enjoy adding subtitles to your videos!